Long time no see, An Qiu
好久不见，安秋
How do you know who I am?
你怎么知道我是谁？
because
因为
I'm your partner
我是你的伙伴
What does it mean
这是什么意思
shanty town
棚户区
We were arrested together
我们一起被捕
Run
跑跑
Bright-eyed people are here
眼睛明亮的人就在这里
Don't move, let me go
别动，让我走
I'm waiting
我在等待
noon the day after tomorrow
后天中午
See you at the same place
在同一个地方见
If you want to know all the answers
如果你想知道所有的答案
chew
嚼
morning
早晨
What's wrong
怎么了
Why did you want to kill Qin Xinhui?
为什么要杀秦心慧？
exhibit
展示
Maybe Lu Yan led us in the wrong direction
或许吕燕把我们引错了方向
Yin Tianhong’s goal is not the laboratory
殷天鸿的目标不是实验室
But the robot
但机器人
How else could Chen Xinhui explain it?
陈新辉还能如何解释呢？
It has nothing to do with the laboratory
和实验室没有关系
And Yin Tianhong doesn't know her either
而殷天鸿也不认识她
Maybe it was after Yin Tianhong saw the news
也许是殷天鸿看到新闻后
Know that Chen Xinhui is a robot
知道陈新辉是机器人
That's why I killed her
这就是我杀了她的原因
Then after he killed someone
然后他杀了人之后
Why were the bodies taken away?
为什么要带走尸体？
Arrange like your twin sign
像你的双生星座一样排列
Simply perverted
简直就是变态
Every crime has its logic
每一种犯罪都有其逻辑
So the problem is we don't know the logic now
所以问题是我们现在不知道逻辑
That's why I'm stuck here
这就是为什么我被困在这里
This is because of Lu Yan
这是因为卢燕
We didn't get any professional resume reports at all.
我们根本没有得到任何专业的简历报告。
It only contains the identification information of the test subjects.
上面只有试验对象的身份信息。
what do you think
你怎么认为
do you know him?
你认识他吗？
You will send the next batch of bots for testing
您将发送下一批机器人进行测试
What's up with him?
他怎么了？
We doubt
我们怀疑
All the robots are in the lab
所有的机器人都在实验室里
They were all killed by him
他们都被他杀了
Who is Yin Tianhong's employer?
尹天鸿的雇主是谁？
what kind of person is he
他是一个什么样的人
What is primary mania?
什么是原发性躁狂？
speak out
说出来
Information about all robots in the lab
有关实验室中所有机器人的信息
give me everything
把所有东西都给我
Yes, I gave you everything.
是的，我把一切都给了你。
are you sure
你确定吗
certainly
当然
let's go
我们走吧
chew
嚼
You're acting strange today
你今天表现得很奇怪
When she had just deceived Lu Yan
当她刚刚骗过陆宴的时候
I've never seen you so fierce
我从未见过你如此凶猛
I just want to find Yin Tianhong quickly
我只想快点找到殷天鸿
correct
正确的
When did your mother start building the laboratory?
你妈妈什么时候开始建实验室的？
Not long after Mingmu was established, she joined
明目成立不久，她就加入了
I've been very busy since then
从那以后我一直很忙
It seems I'm trying
看来我是在尝试
she said here
她在这里说
That was at Dreamland Club
那是在梦境俱乐部
dream club
梦境俱乐部
What on earth is this place?
这到底是什么地方？
I remember before the subpoena was issued.
我记得在发出传票之前
The media has exposed
有媒体曝光过
Provided is an interesting android project
提供的是一个有趣的 android 项目
Should we go there and check it out?
我们应该去那里看看吗？
Something must have happened there
那里一定发生了什么事情
Who are you?
你是谁？
Who are you
你是谁
I'm a temporary cleaner
我是临时清洁工
welcome
欢迎
We are sharp-eyed investigators
我们是目光敏锐的调查员
Is this the Dreamland Club?
这是梦境俱乐部吗？
We are investigating the case
我们正在调查此案
Can you take us there?
可以带我们去吗？
he goes
他走
This has been closed for a long time
这个已经关闭很久了
what are you doing here?
你在这里做什么？
When I close this
当我关闭这里之后
Will it always be empty?
会永远是空的吗？
After what happened, they all ran away.
发生事情后，他们都逃跑了。
No one cares anymore
没人再关心了
everyone ran away
大家都逃跑了
So who will take care of you?
那谁来照顾你呢？
This is commissioned by the broker.
这是受经纪人委托的。
Let me see you every few days
让我每隔几天来看你一次
As long as the house is good
只要房子好
You just said something happened here
你刚刚说这里发生了一些事情
What happened that year?
那一年发生了什么？
Have you heard of Dreamland Club?
你听说过梦境俱乐部吗？
we only know
我们只知道
The following are the functions of Android system
以下是安卓系统的功能
I'm not sure
我不太确定
before issuing a subpoena
在发出传票之前
The owner of this club
这个俱乐部的老板
Looking for a fleet of robot receptionists
寻找一群机器人接待员
This is a regular club during the day
这是白天的常规俱乐部
Night comes
夜一来临
So the receptionist was replaced by a robot.
所以接待员被机器人取代了。
Android later became known as
安卓后来被称为
Android receptionists are becoming less common
Android 接待员变得越来越少
I didn't expect anyone to come here looking for updates.
我没想到有人来这里寻找更新。
On the contrary, more and more
相反，越来越多
What types of services are provided?
提供什么类型的服务？
how could I know
我怎么知道
I'm just a cleaner
我只是一名清洁工
here
这里
A woman was stabbed more than a dozen times
一名女子被刺十几刀
Bodies were dumped here.
尸体被扔在这里。
Is she also a guest at the club?
她也是俱乐部的客人吗？
What is contact information
什么是联系方式
I have no idea
我不知道
You should ask the police about this.
这件事你应该向警察询问。
you know where people die
你知道人们死在哪里
I just don't know her identity
我只是不知道她的身份
What should be said and what should not be said
什么该说，什么不该说
you have a very clear mind
你有一个非常清晰的头脑
Have you caught the murderer?
你抓到凶手了吗？
No
不
It was later discovered that the deceased was an android.
后来发现死者是一个仿生人。
The case is over
此案已结束
Android
安卓
Cheng Nu
程女
This should be your twins horoscope
这应该是你的双胞胎占星图
ritual murder
仪式谋杀
maybe start from here
也许从这里开始
But I always feel like something is missing
但我总觉得缺了点什么
something is missing
缺了点什么
cluster
星团
exhibit
展示
when the murder occurred
谋杀案发生时
Yin Tianhong should be there too
殷天鸿应该也在
This is the address Sister Qiao told you
这是乔姐告诉你的地址
correct
正确的
How does she know everything?
她怎么知道一切？
That's it
就是这样
What's wrong
怎么了
Sister Gu sent photos of death at the scene
顾姐发来现场死亡照片
The deceased in Dream Club was named Luo Su
梦境俱乐部死者名叫罗苏
The murderer strangled her to death
凶手将她勒死后
I have dozens of extra packages
我有几十个额外的包裹
This is perverted
这很变态
Your name is Tang Min
你叫唐敏
We are sharp-eyed investigators
我们是目光敏锐的调查员
Dream Club a year ago
梦境俱乐部 一年前
The robot is dead
机器人死了
Was it you who went to identify the body?
是你去辨认尸体的吧？
Come and drink some water
过来喝点水
Thanks
谢谢
excuse me
打扰一下
We are here to ask about Luosu.
我们来这里是为了询问罗苏的情况。
your house is beautiful
你的房子很漂亮
It is said
据说
I've worked in clubs before.
我以前也曾在俱乐部工作过。
Yes, I used to work as a cashier there.
是的，我曾经在那里当收银员。
I heard that you and Luo Su have a good relationship.
听说你和罗苏关系很好。
Because these are the guests who come to the club to spend money
因为这些都是来俱乐部花钱的客人
He often bullies others just because he has money.
他经常因为有钱就欺负别人。
It stops it for me every time
它每次都帮我阻止了它
Did you know this is Android?
你知道这是安卓吗？
nightclub receptionist
夜总会接待员
They are all Android
他们都是安卓的
Rossu is also a receptionist
罗苏也是一名接待员
She was one of the first receptionists
她是最早的接待员之一
when i leave
当我走的时候
She has been working there for a long time
她已经在那里工作很长时间了
you are in the club
你在俱乐部
Have you met this person?
你见过这个人吗？
He is also the receptionist
他也是接待员
What is his relationship with Luo Su?
他和罗苏是什么关系？
Both
两个都
They shouldn't know each other, right?
他们应该不认识吧？
Russell was seriously ill at the time
当时罗素病重
Then I left the club
然后我离开了俱乐部
A few months later this guy came
几个月后这个人来了
no intersection
没有交集
What kind of person is Yin Tianhong?
殷天鸿是一个什么样的人？
this person
这个人
I'm not very familiar with this.
我对此不太熟悉。
So why does he want to work at Dreamland Club?
那么他为什么要去梦境俱乐部工作呢？
Why are you interested in it?
你为什么对它感兴趣？
We have been looking for Yin Tianhong
我们一直在寻找殷天鸿
But found almost nothing
但几乎什么也没发现
any useful information
任何有用的信息
I felt a little anxious for a while
一时间我感到有点着急
excuse me
打扰一下
I don't know either
我也不知道
Why did he come to the club?
他为什么来俱乐部？
Probably because after the subpoena was announced
可能是因为传票宣布后
There are probably a lot of Android devices out there that don’t want to go back.
可能有很多安卓设备不想回去。
The club is one of the few that can offer robots
该俱乐部是少数可以提供机器人的俱乐部之一
Provide a place to work
提供工作场所
You just said that Luo Su was sick
你刚才说罗苏有病
she has lupus erythematosus
她患有红斑狼疮
this is very dangerous
这是非常危险的
that's why she is
这就是为什么她是
Expelled from the club
被俱乐部开除
So how did she die in the club?
那么她是怎么死在俱乐部里的呢？
I do not know why either
我也不知道为什么
you never doubted
你从未怀疑过
Who is the murderer?
凶手是谁？
Of course I also have questions
当然我也有疑问
But people in the company
但公司里的人
I'm worried this will affect the company's work
我担心这会影响公司的工作
Then let's all shut up and stop talking.
那我们就都闭嘴，别再说话了。
This matter is over.
这件事已经结束了。
But not long after
但没过多久
Clubs remain closed
俱乐部仍保持关闭状态
Since Luo Su was brought to Xiyuan
自从洛苏被带到西苑后
things are not going well
事情进展不顺利
to the end
到最后
He died mysteriously
他离奇死亡
I don't even know why he died.
我什至不知道他为什么死。
Yin Tianhong and Luo Su
殷天红和罗苏
It's time to enter the Dreamland Club
是时候进入梦境俱乐部了
No intersection at all
根本没有交集
If Yin Tianhong kills her
如果殷天鸿杀了她
Why?
为什么？
Insufficient motive and insufficient evidence.
动机不足，证据不足。
Maybe Rossu
可能是罗苏
When I returned to Dreamland Club, I met him by chance.
回到梦境俱乐部的时候，我偶尔遇见了他。
If you only see him occasionally
如果你只是偶尔见到他
Why is he a killer?
为什么他是杀手？
He stabbed him several times
他刺伤了他好几刀
so you think
所以你认为
He is not a killer
他不是杀手
I just want to
只是想
Things may not be as simple as we think
事情可能并不像我们想象的那么简单
We were trapped in a shantytown together.
我们一起被困在棚户区。
If you want to know all the answers
如果你想知道所有的答案
noon the day after tomorrow
后天中午
See you at the same place
在同一个地方见
I know you will definitely come
我知道你一定会来
I'm not here for you today
我今天不是为了你而来
for truth
为了真理
those robots
那些机器人
Did you kill him?
你杀了他吗？
Why
为什么
save them
拯救他们
Help them get rid of their major problems
帮助他们摆脱主要的困扰
Stop making excuses for your deviations
别再为自己的偏差找借口
They don't need you to save them at all
他们根本不需要你来拯救
Because of her initial obsession, Qin Xinhui
因为最初的执念，秦心慧
trying to displace buyers
试图取代买家
Even her son Fang Yuan
就连她的儿子方源
He killed his mother with his own hands
他亲手杀死了他的母亲
Do you think this is true?
你认为这是真的吗？
So you killed her
所以你杀了她
I said that
我说了
I save them
我救他们
After killing Li Yi
杀死李毅后
I was originally going to leave Xiyuan City
我本来是要离开西元城的
but i never thought about it
但我从来没有想过
I can see you in the hospital
我可以在医院见到你
You will be our last hope
你将是我们最后的希望
Where is Luosu?
洛苏呢？
That's what you do, isn't it?
你就是这么做的，不是吗？
when i was thrown into the club
当我被扔进俱乐部的时候
It sucked all the blood out of me
它吸干了我体内所有的血液
if you really kill me
如果你真的杀了我
Why are you so harsh on her?
你为什么对她这么严厉？
Still need to make up a lot of cuts
还需要补很多刀
she
她
the only person i ever loved
我唯一爱过的人
I don't want that, I don't want that
我不想要那个，我不想要那个
next person
下一个人
In no mood
不想
Come and park your car
快来停车
Robot trapped in shantytown
机器人被困在棚户区
All sent to Ming's headquarters
全部送到了明某总部
but i don't know why
但我不知道为什么
we have a group of people
我们有一群人
He was secretly moved to another location
他被秘密转移到另一个地点
Every day people are taken for interrogation
每天都有人被带去审问
suffer mental torture
遭受精神折磨
I am not immune
我也未能幸免
They often put pressure on me
他们经常给我压力
Challenging the end result in different ways
以不同的方式挑战最终结果
Can you stop asking?
你能别再问了吗？
They tortured me mentally and physically
他们对我进行心理和肉体上的折磨
Until one day I heard them talking
直到有一天我听到他们说话
Several test subjects have died recently
几名测试对象最近死亡
So what's going on with Ming?
那么明某那边到底是怎么回事？
The boss said not to worry, he would take care of it.
老板说不用担心，他会处理的。
She said her eyes were bright
她说眼睛明亮
Let's trust humanity again
让我们再次相信人类
In fact, they already have mites in them.
事实上，它们里面已经有螨虫了。
Humans can never be trusted
人类永远不能被信任
Why did you open the door?
你为什么开门？
I've opened the door
我已经开门了
Everyone, run quickly
大家快跑
One night my friend broke the door lock
一天晚上，我的朋友打破了门锁
Then we have a chance to escape
那时我们才有机会逃脱
After escaping from the underground laboratory
从地下实验室逃出后
I've been hiding
我一直躲着
If this is the case
如果是这样
He was the first person to help me
他是第一个帮助我的人
It also made me feel the world for the first time
也让我第一次感受到这个世界
Someone still cares about me
还是有人关心我
You guessed my identity
你猜到了我的身份
She told me she was a robot too
她告诉我她也是一个机器人
Enter
进入
Sit anywhere
随便坐
What are you avoiding?
你在躲避什么？
My home is relatively simple
我家比较简单
But it's better than living abroad
但总比在国外生活好
If you don't mind, just sleep on the sofa.
不介意的话就睡沙发吧
speak out
说出来
What do you want me to do for you?
你想让我为你做什么？
I ask you to help me wipe my face clean
我请你帮我把脸擦干净
I spent this moment with you too
我也和你一起度过了这一刻
If only someone had helped me.
如果当时有人帮助我就好了。
What medicine did you take this time?
这次吃什么药了？
vitamins
维生素
I'm hungry
我饿了
Have a meal
吃饭
if something happens
如果发生什么事
you must tell me
你必须告诉我
It's cold whether you eat it or not.
不管吃不吃都凉了
Take medicine to the hospital
带药去医院
Let's go to the hospital to get medicine
我们去医院拿药吧
Come
来
come drink water
来喝水吧
lupus erythematosus
红斑狼疮
incurable disease
不治之症
Going to the hospital is a waste of money
去医院就是浪费钱
i can find more jobs
我可以找到更多工作
Now except Dreamland Club
现在除了梦境俱乐部
Who dares to work for us?
谁敢给我们打工？
Look, this idiot is still here.
你看，这个白痴还在这里。
Still in love?
还是有恋情吗？
Do you really think of yourself as a person?
你真的认为自己是一个人
How long have you been waiting for me?
你等我多久了？
this is a love
这是一场恋爱
and gifts
和礼物
give it back to me
把它还给我
oops
哎呀
Android devices can actually write love letters
Android设备其实可以写情书
a love letter
一封情书
Thoughts for everyone
给大家的想法
Meow meow
喵喵
Received love letter for the first time
第一次收到情书
Dear Sue
亲爱的苏
Be serious, be serious
认真一点，认真一点
You are the first person to be nice to me
你是第一个对我好的人
He was also the first person to enter my heart
他也是第一个走进我心里的人
when i write this letter
当我写这封信时
i fall deeply in love with you
我深深地爱上了你
i can do anything for you
我可以为你做任何事
very influential
非常有影响力
so you think
所以你认为
my love for you is real
我对你的爱是真实的
tear well
撕得好
throw it in his face
扔到他脸上
Do you really think we are in love?
你真的认为我们相爱吗？
I'm just kidding you
我只是和你开玩笑
This is our little game in the land of dreams
这是我们梦想之地的小游戏
I'll let you go now
我现在就让你走
Never go back to dreamland again
再也不会回到梦乡
Apparently we are all robots
显然我们都是机器人
Why do you hurt me more?
为什么你更伤害我？
but they are of the same type
但它们是同一类型的
i believe everything
我相信一切
It’s all because of the initial obsession
都是因为最初的执念
You know what my first obsession was?
你知道我最初的痴迷是什么吗？
I was playing with the boys.
是和男生一起玩的
I wouldn't change this
我不会改变这个
I'm just tired of playing with you
我只是厌倦了和你一起玩
Do you still want to help me?
你还想帮我吗？
Please help yourself
请自行帮助自己
roll
卷
Because of her initial obsession
因为她最初的执念
and kana
和卡纳
Don't you think so?
你不这么认为吗
Robots are surrounded by primal obsessions
机器人被原始的痴迷所包围
twisted
扭曲的
they will hurt others
他们会伤害别人
I can't be myself again
我无法再次做回我自己
I've given them a chance before
我之前就给过他们机会
But no one can break through his original obsession
却无人能突破他最初的执念
I can only save them
我只能拯救他们
I don't know Luo Su
我不认识罗苏
Did I really cheat on you?
我真的欺骗了你吗？
but kill it
但杀掉它
Unable to save
无法保存
I can't even save you
我什至无法拯救你
An Qiu, do you know?
安秋，你知道吗？
You are still the same as before
你还是和以前一样
very happy
非常愉快
at least i still remember
至少我还记得
The look in the eyes of the person who hurt me
伤害我的人的眼神
but you forgot
但你忘了
What does it mean
这是什么意思
Do you still remember your brother Anyang?
你还记得你的哥哥安阳吗？
my brother
我的兄弟
Open
打开
I'm already in the shanty town
我已经在棚户区了
I got to know you and Anyang
我认识了你和安阳
At that time, your name was not An Qiu.
那时，你不叫安秋。
and called Anqing
并给安庆打电话
until
直到
Run
跑跑
Someone with bright eyes is coming, hurry up
眼睛明亮的人来了，快点
You are an infertile couple
你们是一对不育夫妇
by order
按订单
What I care about most is loving my family
我最关心的是爱我的家人
Why do you want to arrest me?
你为什么要逮捕我？
do not move
别动
After the subpoena is issued
传票发出后
The couple left you
这对夫妇离开了你
So what can you love?
那么你能爱什么呢？
All that's left is each other.
剩下的就只剩下彼此了
But when that day comes
但当那一天到来时
you can't even do that anymore
你甚至不能再这样做了
quickly
快速地
sit
坐
I ask you to sit down
我请你坐下
Don't run
别跑
Come on, run, run
来吧，跑吧，跑吧
Where is my brother?
我哥哥在哪里？
Kraft
卡夫
stop and be honest
停止并诚实
Big brother
大哥
Brother, wake up
兄弟，醒醒吧
look at me
看着我
Big brother
大哥
who is this
这是谁
who killed him
谁杀了他
Cheng Nu
程女
Why should I believe you?
我为什么要相信你？
Is he hiding something from you?
他是不是有什么事瞒着你？
About raiding shantytowns
关于扫荡棚户区
chew
嚼
It's okay if you don't believe me
如果你不相信我也没关系
But have you ever thought about it?
但你有没有想过？
Why are your memories fading?
为什么你的记忆会消失？
Why did you come to Mingmu?
你为什么来明穆？
you are a robot
你是机器人
Do you know what to do now?
你知道现在该怎么办吗？
I can help you
我可以帮你
Shen Li
沉李
How long have you known An Qiu?
你认识安秋多久了？
nearly half a year
近半年时间
What's wrong
怎么了
You should graduate earlier than her, right?
你应该比她早毕业吧？
Yes
是的
How did you two meet?
你们两个是怎么认识的？
We met in a lecture at school
我们是在学校的一次讲座中认识的
Her professional performance is very good
她的专业表现非常好
I originally planned to stay
本来是打算留下来的
Psychological clinic training
心理诊所培训
Then Mingmu came
然后明穆来了
cooperation with you
与您合作
Why do you ask this?
你为什么问这个？
It's okay, let's meet my partner
没关系，让我们来认识一下我的伙伴
What was the past like in school?
学校里的过去又是怎样的呢？
Did I mention that to you?
我有向你提到过吗？
She only said her family was abroad
她只说她的家人在国外
have nothing to say
没什么好说的
What happened to An Qiu?
安秋怎么了？
Suddenly you care about her
突然你很关心她
That's okay, I still have work to do.
没关系，我还有工作要做。
welcome
欢迎
Please contact me
请联系我
Owner WestX00120
业主西X00120
Ask him if he has a rear driving recorder
问他有没有后置行车记录仪
Where are you
你在哪
at home
在家里
That day in the hospital
那天在医院
Have you really never met Yin Tianhong?
你真的没见过殷天鸿吗？
No
不